NGWA FRANK NEBA FULL STACK DEVELOPER

+237 673220094



frankneba92@gmail.com



Bamenda Cameroon



Ngwa Frank

SUMMARY

I am a full stack Developer with over 4 years of experience and a mastery of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, Python and Django. I have some knowledge in C and C++ with knowledge on version control systems like Git and Github. I have worked on many projects for many different satisfied customers and with different individuals in building user friendly and easily navigated websites and applications. While learning and improving on my skills I have been providing others with the knowledge I have especially knowledge on C to students going in for GCE advance level. I am looking forward to working and collaborating with others in completing projects and expanding my skill set.

EDUCATION

2023 - present

National Higher Polytechnic Institute Bamenda Bachelor in Computer Engineering

2020 - 2023

Progressive Compressive High School Bamenda Science

2013 - 2016

Government High School Bafut

SKILLS

- Good communication skills.
- CSS
- Fluent in English language.
- Javascript
 Respects dateline for tasks given.
- React.js
- · Comfortable working remotely.
- C
- Effective in problem solving
- C++
- Python
- Django

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend web developer

Zilotech, 2023 - Present

- Comprehensive administrative assistance to Management.
- Building friendly user interfaces and scalable web apps.
- Built websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript with frameworks like Bootstrap and react is
- Collabotes with team members in building backend products with
- Implemted responsive designs and improved user interfaces of websites

Freelancer

2020 - Present

- Built websites for over 100 different customers with HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Applied responsive design to produce beautiful views for both mobile and computers
- Collaborated with others in developing full stack applications
- Updated and maintained backend projects built with Django

CERTIFICATES

- Bachelor in Computer Engineering (pursuing)
- GCE Advance Level General 2023
- Best Student Northwest Region GCE Advance Level General Cameroon 2023

LINKS

GitHub: gitHub.com/frankneba

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ngwa-frank-a88747298

Portfolio: ngwafrank.netlify.app